[Music]
the heart of leadership is really
to gain compassion for oneself and for
other people so that we
can just really get to addressing
problems from a heartfelt space
instead of fear
we've got a great cross-section of
students in here we've got
teachers who just want to be better
teachers there's some who are aspiring
to be principals or there
are some who are working in business or
they're working in other industries
they have an understanding that good
leadership is how we connect with other
people
but also to be able to hold a good
relationship with ourselves
[Music]
they're learning lots of mindfulness
techniques they're learning how to
listen to themselves so it might be
through moving the body
it might be through breath it might be
through walking it's through eating
so they're learning those skills and
we're practicing them here so they'll be
better able to use them out in their
work
lots of research has shown that mindful
leaders grow more vertically
and that they're able to deal with
stressors better they're
able to calm themselves faster they're
better listeners
they also are able to be inspired
and be more creative because they're
able to listen they're able to
take in information